{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"c9aeb1b7-665b-46bf-b5ad-2580a17b954a"},"exam":{"id":"f7e9398c-6638-46f7-a30d-f02819c9072e","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"0b2dkrmk-derf-tm5u-h127-w4yffwtldij2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are Support Levels offered by AWS?","explanation":"AWS Support has four levels. Basic is their free entitlement for all AWS Customers. The three paid support plans in order of ascending cost are Developer, Business, and Enterprise. Start-up and Individual do not exist as Support Plans","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"3263b7364a2b2cb3d4697003ef512748","text":"Start-up","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":true}]},{"id":"3a04d665-f391-4b59-93bc-8e7e60565b99","domain":"tech","question":"Your project manager (PM) tasked you with launching an instance for a web application to be developed for an NGO. The PM is especially interested in using an AWS service that provides predicable monthly pricing, and he expects the instance to have the ability to burst above the baseline level of CPU performance when needed. What AWS service should you use to launch this instance?","explanation":"Although EC2 could have been the correct answer, two things are key here: Predicable monthly pricing and instance ability to burst above the baseline level of CPU performance when needed. Lightsail accomplishes that; EC2 is more suitable for consistently high CPU performance, and costs vary according to usage.","links":[{"url":"https://lightsail.aws.amazon.com/ls/docs/en_us/articles/amazon-lightsail-frequently-asked-questions-faq","title":"Frequently Asked Questions in Amazon Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":true},{"id":"1dd30e8d60c2a200781dbcc9286f0919","text":"Elasticsearch Service","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true},{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true}]},{"id":"ij3guy5r-65pf-5sad-nyrn-vkpusbdxd3cz","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services can assist you with cost optimization?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor can assist you with the cost optimization of your AWS environment.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true}]},{"id":"w53824dy-uk0y-a0r6-b6eu-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Yourself and a colleague both want to create a bucket called \"myawsomebucket\" to store your study notes - will you both be able to do this?","explanation":"As S3 bucket names are global, they need to be globally unique meaning you and your colleague cannot have two buckets with the same name, no matter the circumstances","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon S3?"}],"answers":[{"id":"bafd7322c6e97d25b6299b5d6fe8920b","text":"No","correct":true},{"id":"3de7dd4f2d662d5eecc35fa4eadaa8c8","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"e90d556314ed67ac2dcf70aa2bd7fefd","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"93cba07454f06a4a960172bbd6e2a435","text":"Yes","correct":false}]},{"id":"19ddf237-f79d-4d25-b0ae-81419166300b","domain":"security","question":"Enabling Amazon GuardDuty automatically grants this service the permission to analyze which of the following data sources?","explanation":"Amazon GuardDuty monitors the security of your AWS environment by analyzing and processing three data sources, which are VPC Flow Logs, AWS CloudTrail event logs, and DNS logs.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/guardduty/latest/ug/what-is-guardduty.html","title":"What is GuardDuty?"}],"answers":[{"id":"6b7cef11406f2fff58dcc619a2b7e482","text":"Amazon S3 buckets","correct":false},{"id":"da9b46af667cf2279d002b955813bb34","text":"AWS CloudTrail logs","correct":true},{"id":"8db8c2b0bbd0ff71d1d15bb32f69e3b8","text":"VPC Flow Logs","correct":true},{"id":"a70a14359eb44629c70e41470e05570f","text":"DNS query logs","correct":true}]},{"id":"mlqp7x88-xfgl-3xkm-trto-wx59uhf7dox6","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below allows you to restrict access to individual objects in an S3 bucket? ","explanation":"Access Control Lists let you control access to individual objects within an S3 bucket, whereas Bucket Policies allow you to control access to entire buckets. In relation to S3, Bucket Control Lists and Access Policies do not exist as configuration items.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/using-iam-policies.html","title":"About S3 Bucket Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"64d03326bddfa39f7ae9a129e8b731c6","text":"Bucket Access Lists","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":true},{"id":"7cfde5ee620a2532233ca18a68fd35ba","text":"Bucket Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"8eaf761b0344c54cfcf063cb006e4ad1","text":"Access Policies","correct":false}]},{"id":"riqpy09p-2mos-4v71-m59a-je7iknttb5c4","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following is generally not billed for on the AWS platform?","explanation":"Data Transferred in to AWS is almost always free of charge (excluding large transfer services, like AWS Snowball). The reason for this, and best way to remember it is that AWS don't mind you transferring lots of data in to their services, since you'll already be paying to use and store it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false},{"id":"8c4aa541ee911e8d80451ef8cc304806","text":"Storage","correct":false},{"id":"a5227beaedc6d59181cd9199f25d32ce","text":"Data-out","correct":false},{"id":"72a2694d2bcec74cfbc3e76e2e8d6c24","text":"Data-in","correct":true}]},{"id":"alwhmkiv-aa40-zbsb-1app-zkbeiem7zvs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, for which of the following does AWS not assume responsibility?","explanation":"Customers are responsible for their own customer data in the cloud. AWS manages the Networking, Hypervisor Configuration, and Physical Security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"1b837a3c0786d704da0c00c61b4d57b5","text":"Hypervisors","correct":false},{"id":"5dd5aedeaa5de8a95f383a8e014b1e5d","text":"Physical security of AWS facilities","correct":false},{"id":"a5fa5746370b608090b994a97b49e98b","text":"Networking","correct":false},{"id":"6016c2bb7bd8dd79293094d37ebfea3f","text":"Customer data","correct":true}]},{"id":"57d67272-2fbd-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"What is the maximum amount of storage that Amazon Aurora offers?","explanation":"With each database instance launched in AWS, Aurora can auto-scale up to 64 TB when needed.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What Is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c1edd650c09defc6ca8d0aaf67803ddc","text":"64 TB","correct":true},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"911ede8df5585598c294830dafe276fa","text":"32 GB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false}]},{"id":"f3458221-d64a-4bbb-b337-65aa47b1614e","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following does Amazon assure will happen when paying for AWS on an as-needed basis?","explanation":"Amazon provides certain benefits when you pay for services on an as-needed basis for your business. You can spend more time innovating and inventing, which consequently reduces the complexity of procurement and enables your business to be fully elastic. ","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"4657fb4ee914ab51c07ee5913b69cb48","text":"Reducing procurement complexity","correct":true},{"id":"48a2453a766bcd12a90a271271ca86a5","text":"Redirecting focus to innovation and invention","correct":true},{"id":"8c0088e02946138166ef2d9e4bf9ab82","text":"Spending less money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"d2c91d7ba7466b41bdbcd42e13db2ecb","text":"Spending more money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"805b488dc48f4591141569966cee0a89","text":"Enabling the full elasticity of business operations","correct":true}]},{"id":"6ffbb1ad-0c02-4ae3-82ba-fa79a62e733b","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support pricing plans provide access to both the AWS Personal Health Dashboard and the AWS Health API?","explanation":"Having an AWS account grants you access to the Personal Health Dashboard to receive alerts and remediation guidance regarding events affecting the services underlying your resources. However, if you go with either the Business or Enterprise support plan, you will also get AWS Health API for integrating health data and notifications with your existing in-house and third-party IT management tools.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/health/latest/APIReference/Welcome.html","title":"What is AWS Health?"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"pt61wdfy-tnhp-k8r7-te3l-vczb6trwu4x5","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below statements about Amazon VPC is most accurate?","explanation":"Amazon VPC allows you to build a private, virtual network in the AWS cloud, affords you complete control of network configuration, and offers several layers of security controls.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"About VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"c543f2f72255495cbbc56ce672d12564","text":"Amazon VPC offers several layers of security controls.","correct":false},{"id":"15b3b217cc17fcdf1461509394ea0664","text":"Amazon VPC allows you to build a private, virtual network in the AWS cloud.","correct":false},{"id":"f861cb51390cd12273087e488f8be68b","text":"Amazon VPC offers none of these features.","correct":false},{"id":"ca15e10364461b0878a8e25af87638ec","text":"Amazon VPC offers all of these features.","correct":true},{"id":"b32bdcf3a762c1d6a2c979ee4fd5e2d8","text":"Amazon VPC affords you complete control of network configuration.","correct":false}]},{"id":"wdqr2l66-jcd9-o6lx-b012-qodibilagwi2","domain":"tech","question":"You need to implement an automated service that will scan your AWS environment with the goal of both improving security and reducing costs. Which service should you use?","explanation":"An online resource to help you reduce cost, increase performance, and improve security by optimizing your AWS environment, Trusted Advisor provides real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"9633b701743bf40ce928fb9fa4c0ed66","text":"Config Rules","correct":false},{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"0bcfa28115476b2bcfed146f27c465c4","text":"Service Catalog","correct":false}]},{"id":"wfisjo0f-usp3-160k-im9l-di4ay4ny42e8","domain":"tech","question":"Which AWS service is specifically designed to assist you in processing large data sets?","explanation":"Elastic Map Reduce (EMR) is a service that makes it easy to process large amounts of data efficiently. Redshift is a data warehousing solution. ElastiCache is used for caching data in memory for high speed read-access. EC2 is a general purpose compute service for hosting virtual servers. Whilst you could run big data processing tasks on EC2, it will be easier on EMR, which has been designed specifically for this purpose","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/emr/","title":"About EMR"}],"answers":[{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"be94b3c024501e2d7e9e64f4e0d18af9","text":"Elastic Map Reduce (EMR)","correct":true},{"id":"50848259480914860b338e7baf94c29a","text":"ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false}]},{"id":"77471ce7-4336-4912-9c33-ecfc5d174a41","domain":"billing","question":"You want to monitor your costs of using your AWS services and receive alerts when the thresholds you defined are met. Which of the following AWS Budget types should you create?","explanation":"You need to create a cost budget with AWS Budgets if you want to monitor the cost of using your AWS services.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/budgets-managing-costs.html","title":"Managing Your Costs with Budgets"}],"answers":[{"id":"825a98fa534bb772e00d7b7571f0217f","text":"Reservation Budget","correct":false},{"id":"bd4ad96569591af6420d456b8176c90d","text":"Savings Plans Budget","correct":false},{"id":"3f3eb4d8c9ecc531c5a784bcc5e608b5","text":"Usage Budget","correct":false},{"id":"7d45335a770dd2fc66658fb908bb7f9a","text":"Cost Budget","correct":true}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false}]},{"id":"yvxo9l3i-wh4o-2dqm-3mnu-snzqe8qbcn6w","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes an AWS Region?","explanation":"A Region is a distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography. Regions are a key concept in AWS' Global Infrastructure - each is made up of one or more isolated (within that region) Availability Zones. There are often multiple AWS Regions on each continent, such as North America","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"02994d9c387a384eeaa6efd09a6dd102","text":"A distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography.","correct":true},{"id":"cd212d0c12772fef24104f0585e29933","text":"A collection of data centres that are spread evenly around a specific continent.","correct":false},{"id":"8c91beabafc69d771d60455febdc0927","text":"A console that gives you a quick, global picture of your cloud computing environment.","correct":false},{"id":"1230f90d0fb76db29194467e14f8e099","text":"A collection of databases that can only be accessed from a specific geographic region.","correct":false}]},{"id":"5b9adb12-1511-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true about the Amazon EC2 service?","explanation":"All statements are correct save for one. EC2 does not limit the maximum number of virtual servers to 5; you can launch as many of them as you need.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/concepts.html","title":"What Is Amazon EC2?"}],"answers":[{"id":"05abe36774fd4ff06a9e3dbea47f091b","text":"It supplies various configurations of CPU, memory, storage, and network capacity.","correct":true},{"id":"8f29ef75026ce095e4c2bdfef7fda8d4","text":"It provides virtual computing environments.","correct":true},{"id":"749e437b9476936c3592642fdb9ad851","text":"It provides a virtual database environment.","correct":false},{"id":"4e9a1f08edd0d2fc4013ed10e09f571c","text":"It is used to launch up to 5 servers.","correct":false},{"id":"f24b25808e75812b13593ad35b4e87c0","text":"It provides scalable computing capacity in the AWS cloud.","correct":true}]},{"id":"cckhl0ep-pmhf-g8be-yplb-dzr17jgnk6mn","domain":"security","question":"Where is the best place to store your Root User Access Key so that your application can use it to make requests to AWS?","explanation":"It is not recommended to use Root User account or access keys for any reason as these grant full unrestricted access to the entire account. Recommended practice is to follow the concept of \"Least Privilege\" and create am IAM user or role with just enough access to do what is needed and nothing more, and use those keys as required","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws-access-keys-best-practices.html","title":"Best Practices for Managing AWS Access Keys"}],"answers":[{"id":"73532a5c24d7b4c1df276690bbaedfff","text":"In the .aws file in you application","correct":false},{"id":"2330278fe444dd9a6196cb146c97de7e","text":"Nowhere - you should not use the Root User access keys for this","correct":true},{"id":"9feb4a526584eae16c38880b7813f48c","text":"It needs to be coded directly into your application","correct":false},{"id":"503d72b0254a8561511b71a95f8eb8a7","text":"It should be configured as a parameter and held in the Key Management Store (KMS)","correct":false}]},{"id":"pnvuqf5l-037m-d7re-80px-dktopvvnrkq4","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services should you use to migrate an existing database to AWS?","explanation":"The AWS Database Migration Service is a service specifically designed to support migrations of databases from on-premise into AWS","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dms/","title":"About the AWS Database Migration Service"}],"answers":[{"id":"0893147538c21c827dc499b4852934e3","text":"Route 53","correct":false},{"id":"1d61150ca8c56343cc23363e78429886","text":"AWS DMS","correct":true},{"id":"947642228a6d69446c74618fdde1bfd6","text":"Storage Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"54afc4697cf03d8e3ec9a05b16380622","text":"SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"pzjuwu91-24rb-x77o-tzlj-dzpn3pvo3v3v","domain":"security","question":"You need to use an AWS service to assess the security and compliance of your EC2 instances. Which of the following services should you use?","explanation":"AWS Inspector is an automated security assessment service that helps improve the security and compliance of applications deployed on AWS. AWS Trusted Advisor can give security recommendations about your AWS resources, but not within EC2 instances themselves. AWS Shield and WAF can protect EC2 instances, but don't possess any capabilities to assess their security and compliance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/?nc2=h_m1","title":"About AWS Inspector"}],"answers":[{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false}]},{"id":"xun4oj55-ptum-ekl7-y5ot-pqhc5t5psvxi","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following support plans features unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases?","explanation":"Both Enterprise and Business support plans feature unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]},{"id":"el8zebxq-qo1d-az5o-l4lp-vmh132hnt1zd","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance guarantees attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US?","explanation":"A HIPAA certification attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"},{"url":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippa_(disambiguation)","title":"HIPPA or HIPAA"}],"answers":[{"id":"d0a785d52ac4a841f7efdf0098d9ebd5","text":"HIPAA","correct":true},{"id":"739f96badcfca6fd03c1e5b17971c9de","text":"HIPPO","correct":false},{"id":"827ec26130c30cc52e3fb178e0ef505c","text":"FERPA","correct":false},{"id":"393dceb94f2cac456fd53985a67d72b3","text":"HITECH","correct":false},{"id":"dba5359496e7ea71f51ce4da1ee614bd","text":"GLBA","correct":false}]},{"id":"a4a20c80-1512-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements are true of Amazon Aurora?","explanation":"Amazon Aurora is compatible with MySQL and PostgreSQL, and you can handle routine database tasks on it using either the AWS Management Console, AWS CLI commands, or API operations. As a relational database offering, it is part of the RDS service, not DynamoDB, which is AWS’s nonrelational database service. In addition, Aurora delivers up to five times the throughput of MySQL, not three times.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"542b22f6c50dd511f8e64db1ac734bc6","text":"It is compatible with the MySQL and PostgreSQL database engines.","correct":true},{"id":"87b549b9a5f186a6d978ec037b9d268f","text":"It uses the AWS Management Console, AWS CLI commands, and API operations to handle routine database tasks.","correct":true},{"id":"ca3a9ff8718b6a2ed0c56d839b5313b0","text":"It can deliver up to three times the throughput of MySQL.","correct":false},{"id":"16e59a8af37a34b9625d2d16558ef925","text":"It is part of the Amazon DynamoDB service.","correct":false}]},{"id":"86d0ccb9-ab67-4952-a7ea-0fea12fc6c1f","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to data security in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which includes security. The customer is responsible for who can access the data itself.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"9f02eb6c8050b89db31831403951787b","text":"The customer is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":true},{"id":"6e8271456f0c471167caae0d75aab487","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":false},{"id":"599dca975551e5a41106ce454a46e4e0","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":true},{"id":"7a0bc438686e10d5e1ab102d0dc0e4a9","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":false},{"id":"2844802845f801aded529f1d22c63d82","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":true},{"id":"0ed894aaf38bd44ba33d1612854617d0","text":"AWS is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":false}]},{"id":"84d8ac20-2fb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Once you exceed a usage percentage of Free Tier limits for any service, AWS will automatically send you an email notification. What is that percentage?","explanation":"If you exceed 85% of Free Tier usage, AWS will automatically send you an email to notify you. This is to alert you to help with staying within the Free Tier limits; otherwise, you may incur charges.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"1c383cd30b7c298ab50293adfecb7b18","text":"35","correct":false},{"id":"3ef815416f775098fe977004015c6193","text":"85","correct":true},{"id":"c0c7c76d30bd3dcaefc96f40275bdc0a","text":"50","correct":false},{"id":"d09bf41544a3365a46c9077ebb5e35c3","text":"75","correct":false}]},{"id":"55632ec1-3922-4d04-80c0-ff9b5b21c2d2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are AWS EC2 reserved pricing types?","explanation":"Reserved instances have three main pricing models, Standard, Convertible and Scheduled. Each model is targeted with a specific use case and benefits from its own level of discounted price","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"bd1ad3385adf098b2e87d2bb75d87e39","text":"Scalable Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"c81edad1f6d23ac52025cde1cf22ba7b","text":"Scheduled Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"e507a844b940fd588a1cbb5bb46fd4fe","text":"Standard Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"c9e63a71aa24afcde5e964d2530e2524","text":"Compute Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"fe501a6493589e0d87e90fd0b4361e6f","text":"Convertable Reserved Instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"e4e33d76-4ad4-48e6-8420-50d958d0c8a9","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are part of the AWS storage services category?","explanation":"S3, EFS, and AWS Backup are three of AWS’s storage services. RDS and Redshift are classified as database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"ce52d2cff6e50f2e74505e0c70d072b3","text":"AWS Backup","correct":true},{"id":"35686630aa3baddc18c904374e570233","text":"Amazon RDS","correct":false},{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":true},{"id":"f7b96044a16becafecad63df1725e9c8","text":"Amazon EFS","correct":true},{"id":"f7415e33f972c03abd4f3fed36748f7a","text":"Amazon Redshift","correct":false}]},{"id":"c127gqer-wn02-ljaa-xx5a-jpsogr3yw2ij","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS services are free to use?","explanation":"Whilst all of these services are free to use, the things they create or interact with can incur charges. For instance, a CloudFormation template is free to run, but if it creates an EC2 instance, you will be paying for that EC2 instance. Whilst some of the other services do have free tier entitlements or features, as a service, they do have general costs associated with them","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/services/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"caa58cad8d490fcdf1da0862623481fc","text":"Auto-Scaling","correct":true},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"d85c80578ad0849a611c1056b63e385c","text":"VPC","correct":true},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":true}]},{"id":"e5705f98-2edd-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following falls under the AWS database services category?","explanation":"ElastiCache, which serves as Amazon’s in-memory data store, is the only AWS database service listed here. The others are AWS storage services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"df346128c45efa43efc29607224fc716","text":"Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3)","correct":false},{"id":"d2a6652ddeb631da029d1f2806e11fdc","text":"Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)","correct":false},{"id":"4b21f5ceb7fb3f03f0d53a427f6be836","text":"Amazon FSx","correct":false},{"id":"770b120ec487568871cc9ab64475af46","text":"Amazon ElastiCache","correct":true}]},{"id":"4hjaxq6n-z5w0-zfz5-rhia-l14kd19r6656","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are best practices when it comes to securing your AWS account?","explanation":"Creating individual IAM users, using groups to assign them permission and creating a strong password policy are all key components of securing your AWS account. The root user should only be used in emergencies, therefore there should be no need to have Root Access Keys which allow the root user Programmatic access - any Programmatic access should use something other than the root account. It is not possible to delete the root password, and this should be securely, safely stored and not used in any applications!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"07623cbc5a5f07bde8c94a98256a165f","text":"Use groups to assign permissions.","correct":true},{"id":"5d44464e3d76ef6a6641b8044d7d2525","text":"Activate MFA on the Root Account.","correct":true},{"id":"561f3fa869736d8c37dd07fc1284f00f","text":"Delete your Root access keys.","correct":true},{"id":"427d69ad60aa7d9c68a9214e103fc80a","text":"Delete your Root account password.","correct":false},{"id":"9c2eddf5402bf5f69b4cfd6f6cbb82ef","text":"Store your Root account keys on your application for easy access.","correct":false},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"af5257e2e32921faab688050c9de091e","text":"Apply an IAM password policy.","correct":true}]},{"id":"fd097342-1bc8-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"CloudFront is used to route users to the edge location that provides the lowest amount of time delay in delivering content. Which of the following terms describes this 'time delay'?","explanation":"Latency refers to the amount of time delay during the processing of network data. CloudFront is AWS’s content delivery network service, which routes users to the edge location with the lowest latency. That means the content will be delivered as fast as possible.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/Introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon CloudFront?"}],"answers":[{"id":"314a0d25c2c847aaa07e42887fda1f7b","text":"scalability","correct":false},{"id":"e3cba4d3cce16ddf0ce129e981fb5bc2","text":"resiliency","correct":false},{"id":"aa3d4919f7245b97e2663e9bd2c15100","text":"elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"7883a7305bcbd394f768e04b9e800f53","text":"latency","correct":true}]},{"id":"b419a913-a5f1-4ad2-8c06-3b579643d073","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS responsible for in the Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"AWS manages security of the cloud. This includes the infrastructure, which consists of regions, edge locations, and Availability Zones. On the other hand, security in the cloud is the responsibility of the customer. Therefore, AWS is not responsible for safeguarding customer data; the customer is.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"0b4219abe92a5981f2c74b7a4ec441ab","text":"Customer Data","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":true}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false},{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true},{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false},{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true}]},{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false},{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false},{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true},{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false}]},{"id":"o8aqfsp4-kk6k-gyj7-frq7-4bpn7iv5zqm8","domain":"concepts","question":"You have a mission-critical application which must be globally available at all times. Which deployment strategy should you follow?","explanation":"A Multi-Region deployment will best ensure global availability. While it can be the most expensive, and complex to configure, Multi-Regional architectures will ensure that even if all Availability Zones in a single region fail due to a catastrophic event, your data will remain accessible.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"86b2c5243e03e210528f020bad4efdb9","text":"Multi-VPC in two AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"e4ec2833a31f482abfdb31691f0351dc","text":"Multi-Region","correct":true},{"id":"91d7ff212b9bda483701aeb4209ae5ec","text":"Deploy to all Availability Zones in your home region.","correct":false},{"id":"ec206762c0bea997a5b0f91783cce54f","text":"Multi-Availability Zone","correct":false}]},{"id":"b7755a84-2ede-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services fall under the Migration and Transfer category?","explanation":"Database Migration Service is for migrating databases to AWS, and Snowball is for using devices to transfer large amounts of data in and out of the AWS Cloud. So, both services are Migration and Transfer services. Redshift is Amazon’s data warehouse solution, and ElastiCache is an in-memory data store; both are database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"770b120ec487568871cc9ab64475af46","text":"Amazon ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"c2d838ea2b9043be2161255da328dc60","text":"AWS Snowball","correct":true},{"id":"f7415e33f972c03abd4f3fed36748f7a","text":"Amazon Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"e30020a3e07c8d84a925df2ca76a2af5","text":"AWS Database Migration Service","correct":true}]},{"id":"d6a825a0-2fb8-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Where do you go to for viewing your AWS monthly charges?","explanation":"Information about your AWS monthly charges are provided in the Billing and Cost Management Console. Cost Explorer, Budgets, and Monthly Spend by Linked Account View are actually three features within the Billing and Cost Management console; they are not dashboards that display your monthly charges.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/invoice.html","title":"Viewing Your Monthly Charges"}],"answers":[{"id":"398d49f50aaa9e03a92dd2d3f2c6a389","text":"Billing and Cost Management","correct":true},{"id":"1cc9c00d1383db13dd08ad29b47af362","text":"Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"c11363b7e018c4e9c17fd75fef1e3c58","text":"Monthly Spend by Linked Account View","correct":false},{"id":"619ed6d20397878e9706fe9fa7c44579","text":"Cost Explorer","correct":false}]},{"id":"rc4dwp79-ix5s-h912-sdcj-9gmmhl6zacte","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed DDoS protection service?","explanation":"AWS Shield is AWS' managed DDoS protection service at Layer 4. AWS WAF provides protection from common exploits against your web applications at Layer 7, and does not protect against DDoS attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/?nc2=h_l3_dm","title":"About AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false}]},{"id":"5d7bea17-63ec-412b-bb14-bd0a1f5c4683","domain":"concepts","question":"If you have a new application and you are not sure about future demand, which of the below characteristics of cloud make cloud an ideal place to host it?","explanation":"No upfront & Pay as you go mean that you do not need an initial outlay of capital for resources to build in cloud, and only need to pay for what you use going forward. These combined with the ability to consume more resources when needed (Scalability) mean that cloud is a great way to host applications that have dynamic requirements. No Single Points of Failure and High Availability should be included in any design, but are not intrinsic to cloud. Similarly, although Performance Efficiency is key, this comes down to you application and it's design, and is not a characteristic of the cloud. ","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"e95a95951d99b5f038c688bf69bd5a01","text":"Pay as you go","correct":true},{"id":"5c751a74a73417fb82a2cc45c4edc2cb","text":"No upfront","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"bc368b371822f4e7df28c5768582dde8","text":"Performance Efficiency","correct":false},{"id":"9043a5d84d85473bd60ab9b11f10b04b","text":"No single point of failure","correct":false}]},{"id":"bc537d70-2f37-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following classifications would apply to Kinesis Video Streams?","explanation":"Kinesis Video Streams is an AWS service you can use to store and watch video streams in real time as they are received in the cloud. In addition, you can process and analyze the streams by using third-party solutions that you can get at the AWS Marketplace. So, Kinesis Video Streams is both a media service and an analytics tool.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/kinesisvideostreams/latest/dg/what-is-kinesis-video.html","title":"What Is Amazon Kinesis Video Streams?"}],"answers":[{"id":"091fa9121c047db1dd48c3e2ab5f3c91","text":"Machine Learning","correct":false},{"id":"ac1697f8b440a0a0dca32da2e95da8bd","text":"Media Services","correct":true},{"id":"a768caa988605a2846599cf7e2d0c26a","text":"Analytics","correct":true},{"id":"0b4a1fd2370952e6f7c276106ee02957","text":"Game Development","correct":false}]},{"id":"qlfvvg3n-igqt-be79-1bph-rx4nrjmqmm25","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below statements are correct in relation to security responsibilities in AWS?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud - the security of components that run the cloud service. The customer is responsible for security IN the cloud -- that is, the security of their AWS resources and data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"d1f8c47a806feef1c562619b465cb202","text":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"0369ed76a5e4ccb3887e44fe8a7c8703","text":"AWS is responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"a1b79685a2bbdb6743277416ad663c24","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"7c5f3942078ece3769cd1bcbde2bdabb","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":true}]},{"id":"e9yzvx4u-z9ss-opgg-lwg4-h390rywj4hat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account?","explanation":"IAM (Identity and Access Management) controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account. Security Groups and Access Control Lists are tools within IAM that can help make that control easier to manage. AWS Shield is a separate service that helps protect resources from external attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/","title":"About IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"83246738-477a-40c5-8224-59d739ad6600","domain":"tech","question":"You are a solutions architect working for a New York-based digital marketing company specializing in local SEO. You are tasked with creating an S3 bucket to operate within the US West (N. California) Region. The company wants to name it with the IP address of the SEO Health Checker application that was recently developed for potential clients based in California to get a free website analysis report. Which of these actions would be most appropriate?","explanation":"Bucket names must not be formatted as an IP address. Indeed, each bucket name should be unique across all existing names in Amazon S3. So, following AWS naming rules, name the bucket after the type of data it will store.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"dc1cf44cc05f915cfa69e23237b4e6c0","text":"Simply name the bucket after the Region.","correct":false},{"id":"49336715d3a6034152315aaa72ba1ca2","text":"That shouldn’t be a problem; name the bucket after the web application’s IP address.","correct":false},{"id":"73d20a8bf6fd3ae4e325f0aba2e8a8c6","text":"Use dashes instead of periods in the IP address to comply with bucket naming rules.","correct":false},{"id":"557ad9f77b4777473a400e65c0bc146a","text":"Do not name the bucket after the application’s IP address.","correct":true}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false}]},{"id":"b7d5jc0p-zg8y-0hwp-3cjv-2yxp349xk58p","domain":"security","question":"You want to streamline access management for your AWS administrators by assigning them a pre-defined set of permissions based on their job role - which of the below is the best way to approach this?","explanation":"Using IAM Groups lets you create a list of pre-defined permissions that any user made a part of that group will be granted. Roles are primarily used to grant AWS resources permissions to other AWS resources and generally are not for end-users. Amazon Cognito is a service that help authenticate users to your apps, and not the AWS console itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_groups.html","title":"IAM Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"28639700aadbc704e3daae5ba44ab388","text":"Use Amazon Cognito","correct":false},{"id":"48fb6d39f4c7857dc342d789480a20ea","text":"Use AWS Organizations","correct":false},{"id":"71f7b94ac76ec4aa2860353bc1120591","text":"Use IAM Roles","correct":false},{"id":"ffc1a593680549bf1bc0e966a70f0683","text":"Use IAM Groups","correct":true}]},{"id":"9da21f94-7d9e-4bcf-8c7c-fc97b0634977","domain":"security","question":"Your company has updated its security policies to include cloud workloads as well as those running on-premises. Your manager would like a report of which technologies will require configuration changes. Which of the following will not be included in the report because they are the responsibility of AWS?","explanation":"In the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, AWS in responsible for managing host operating systems. Users are responsible for managing guest operating systems, as well as Security Group Firewalls, Amazon Aurora data encryption, and S3 access control lists.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"63c21f07ff59add0f7e474ef5ec57c2e","text":"Security Group firewalls","correct":false},{"id":"8061595e3a5f2fb2195dd627dd35f5d2","text":"Host operating systems","correct":true},{"id":"64f8358ae4360eddd993acde2d19789c","text":"Amazon Aurora data encryption","correct":false},{"id":"331bd4e2a8ab147e5a6a47e5b9c40d65","text":"S3 Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"ipqdbu85-0egr-7f6l-daqk-ftz6657spa8l","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that is always online — without the need for human intervention?","explanation":"A highly available system is one that is always online — without the need for human intervention. Although Fault Tolerance is closely related to High Availability, FT usually implies a degradation of service without human intervention, unlike HA which is like-for-like.","links":[{"url":"https://media.amazonwebservices.com/architecturecenter/AWS_ac_ra_ftha_04.pdf","title":"Fault Tolerance and High Availability Infographic"}],"answers":[{"id":"35d7975974b40518da5e7f990c6a7d1d","text":"Fault Tolerant","correct":false},{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":true}]},{"id":"97909ec2-34ad-4743-b7cc-ca2c83c62cc1","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"The AWS Free Tier offers some services for free for the first 12 months after signing up for an AWS account. It also offers free trials of select AWS services for a short period. So, usage is governed by these principles. Although there are some service usages that are always free, this does not apply to EC2 Micro instances nor S3 storage of up to 5 GB.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"424553c7a1502a98737dfd15823ee215","text":"Some AWS services are free for the first 12 months following the initial sign-up date to AWS.","correct":true},{"id":"c90c4c865ee803cfa9bbe8e9a2d845c9","text":"Amazon S3 storage of up to 5 GB is always free.","correct":false},{"id":"f60585d833d73cf82fda96da1f19b3e6","text":"Some AWS services come with short-term free trial offers.","correct":true},{"id":"42c6d3d9032dba4f7aea8ddeedde2f6c","text":"You will never be charged for use of EC2 Micro instances.","correct":false}]},{"id":"amvsqat1-leji-kqd6-yu62-421v3dktmzxn","domain":"tech","question":"You need to automate EC2 resource provisioning to meet demand. Which AWS service can help you accomplish this?","explanation":"Auto Scaling allows you to define thresholds, that when reached trigger the deployment of more EC2 resources. Load Balancers allow you to direct the flow of traffic and do not by themselves create other resources.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"e95e5a2a3cc8625bca3d71b817367e2d","text":"Elastic Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"6ff99ccd616e6ba3ca17de8fe56d016a","text":"EC2 container Service","correct":false},{"id":"afd14eb3f151c84e6ef7ab63812b4fbc","text":"Auto Scaling","correct":true}]},{"id":"yhwuezmk-vte7-c3ty-x612-wvd1qi3aw2us","domain":"tech","question":"You’ve been tasked with assessing your AWS infrastructure in terms of cost optimization. Which of the following AWS services would help with this task? ","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor is an online tool that provides you with real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"ee58e6973ab1b8a94d5434399ac85129","text":"Cloud Trail","correct":false},{"id":"bd02384ebb7e76c74ae044ad5cf295c1","text":" AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false}]},{"id":"57f5e909-774f-43b9-9718-c0b61fc8225c","domain":"security","question":"You are currently running an application in a production environment, but you want to ensure that it is free of vulnerabilities. Which of the following AWS services would you need to use?","explanation":"You will need to turn to Amazon Inspector for security assessment. Not only does it identify vulnerabilities in your application, it will also spot deviations from security best practices. AWS Shield and WAF protect the application from attacks that exploit vulnerabilities, rather than identify them. And Trusted Advisor only provides recommendations on how to improve security.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/inspector/latest/userguide/inspector_introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon Inspector?"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"41a831f771ef9bece59ed5160e335ae7","text":"AWS Trusted Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"543096643aa6d28d9fac278e9257783d","text":"Amazon Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"769f2c629067645d4b60e13009500c9f","text":"AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)","correct":false}]},{"id":"7gpfi6zh-od3t-hgmy-7puh-d955spmckv2u","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound cloud design?","explanation":"Build your systems to be scalable, use disposable resources, reduce infrastructure to code, and, please, assume EVERYTHING will fail sooner or later. Servers should be treated like cattle, where the exist to serve a function, and for a generally limited period of time, as opposed to pets which are kept and cared for over very long periods of time. There is no reason to limit the number of 3rd party services, if it makes the most sense in the case of the design at hand. Tightly-coupled components result in hard dependencies between different services, and usually lead to issues with either an applications health, or its scalability.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"31ae780d15d60c68f6689a039e6f3802","text":"Assume *everything* will fail.","correct":true},{"id":"c4feabf8a0fd67917d77220d3b036291","text":"Tightly-coupled components","correct":false},{"id":"af41549605744cf23f27cbc14458bf82","text":"Infrastructure as code","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"9cb4d987bd4d50912c60823480c86972","text":"Treat your servers like pets, not cattle.","correct":false},{"id":"df89f307a97b6ecf5647735dcd89f7c8","text":"Limit the number of 3rd-party services.","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"porkjt4t-1idl-7vgv-mx2b-s6gvayouwvh4","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are advantages of cloud computing?","explanation":"Elasticity, Agility, and the ability to control the variances in your month-to-month expenditure are all advantages of the flexibility of Cloud Computing. You do still need specialist knowledge to deploy solutions in the Cloud, such as AWS Certifications. Large amounts of capital are also not needed due to the consumption model of most cloud services, although you can sometimes use capital expenditure to purchase resources for extended periods of time, such as Reserved Instances in EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"97e11cb086bf1070777e7e3fa1e31877","text":"Requires large amounts of capital","correct":false},{"id":"b6244c70b8f2eb23f7eb82a740202646","text":"No specialist knowledge required","correct":false},{"id":"a0368a69e2586f302d0f3da6bfa3b031","text":"Agility - Decreasing the time to start new services","correct":true},{"id":"230dee0a7da58ba8fbf9dee4e7448de2","text":"Elasticity - you need not worry about capacity.","correct":true},{"id":"e614fc350d8c3730eaca43265d43d9de","text":"Variable expense","correct":true}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false}]},{"id":"bd8ac490-21fe-451e-a3e6-6dfa221fb389","domain":"concepts","question":"Deploying your EC2 instances across multiple AZs will help address which Cloud Concept?","explanation":"Having resources across multiple AZ is one way to design for High Availability - the concept that your services in cloud should be designed to tolerate failures in the underlying cloud infrastructure. AWS allows you to do this by providing Availability Zones - each one is independent from the others, and a failure in one should not impact the others. Therefore, if you deploy your application in 2 instances in 2 AZs, and one of the AZs fails, you will still have 1 instance running your application. Automation relates simplifying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although scaleability and elasticity (the ability to increase resources according to needs and the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) look like they might fit, as we are talking specifically about Multiple AZs in the question High Availability is the more correct answer","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":true}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false}]},{"id":"csqz3fzq-fvxm-wmtm-lq03-1qm6tx6rsm40","domain":"tech","question":"When you upload an object to S3 storage - where will AWS keep it?","explanation":"Any object uploaded to S3 is automatically stored in multiple Availability Zones in the Region in which it was uploaded. This means that if any single AZ in a Region is experiencing issues, objects stored in S3 will still be available. Although objects in S3 can be made to be accessible globally, by default they are always stored in a redundant fashion in only the region they were uploaded, ruling out the other answers.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"e134be4f4ec87c7e4b3a807a60f8332c","text":"In a single, central location within the Region you select.","correct":false},{"id":"d4e7f5d03f7a64d82b49ae9aa1f01716","text":"In multiple Regions across the globe.","correct":false},{"id":"8739ddb65808177938fb8b26c3bede98","text":"In AWS's central global storage site in the us-east-1 Region","correct":false},{"id":"2d3a21e9924efc0317a134b857ee4036","text":"In multiple Availability Zones within the Region you select.","correct":true}]},{"id":"d54df537-f2ee-46a2-b1f4-2c115bdf2044","domain":"concepts","question":"Using Infrastructure as Code is a related of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Infrastructure as Code is a key implementation of Automation in cloud - using Infrastructure as Code allows to quickly and easily deploy and manage your environment without reliance on humans to complete all the tasks. Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, and it allows you to expand out as needed. Elasticity is the ability to go up and down in resources as needed. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"075e3cda-4e62-4381-bb3f-0cd061c73bb3","domain":"security","question":"A purchasing department staff member is setup as an AWS user in the company’s procurement AWS account. At each month-end, the staff member needs access to an application running on EC2 in the company’s accounts payable AWS account to reconcile reports. Which of the following provides the most secure and operationally efficient way to give the staff member access to the accounts payable application?","explanation":"The staff member should be given the ability to assume a role programmatically with the permissions necessary to run the accounts payable application. Setting up another AWS user for the staff member in the accounts payable account will require the presentation of hard credentials programmatically. Both federation and Lambda will require the use of a role as well, but with the added overhead of maintaining Active Directory or the Lambda function.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_common-scenarios.html","title":"Common Scenarios for Roles: Users, Applications, and Services"}],"answers":[{"id":"e9c43624dba6130e04955aabf167b8b2","text":"Have the user request temporary security credentials for the application by assuming a role","correct":true},{"id":"926f9b540e5d5ff596976f059a7c9cbf","text":"Create a user for the staff member in the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"ecd3e317cda9a34ab820e6d6ff70fcf5","text":"Invoke an AWS Lambda function to run the application in the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"00383ff55511da79680a3cfdf7bd7a1b","text":"Configure Active Directory integration so that you can federate the staff member’s access to the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false}]},{"id":"4885465a-c1a0-41e2-8e7d-d6ac27557522","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following comprises an Amazon Machine Image (AMI)?","explanation":"An AMI includes three types of information. There’s the Amazon EBS snapshot or snapshots for backing up EBS volume data to S3, or a template for the root volume of the instance if the AMI is instance-store-backed. There are launch permissions for controlling which AWS accounts can use the AMI to launch an instance. And there’s block device mapping for specifying the volumes to attach to the instance when it’s launched. These are the pieces of information that AMI requires to launch an EC2 instance; the EC2 instance is part of the AMI itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/WindowsGuide/AMIs.html","title":"Amazon Machine Images (AMI) – Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"6f8a7b69b94bd2a5b6d397b35bf7a403","text":"EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"fb7756bd7b1e9872836772b73ccf9aac","text":"Launch permissions","correct":true},{"id":"11d5f5efdfcf29972a22321321560da7","text":"EBS snapshots or root volume template of an EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"1dd2a814eff8bee8cf3e4da0ee6a245e","text":"Block device mapping","correct":true}]},{"id":"922bcb30-a895-4a3f-bb49-94c90e34a5ed","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following services can Amazon CloudWatch use as a target to deliver near real-time streams of system events that describe changes in AWS resources?","explanation":"EC2 instances, AWS Lambda functions, and Amazon SQS queues are a few of the AWS services that can be configured as targets for CloudWatch events.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/events/WhatIsCloudWatchEvents.html","title":"What Is Amazon Cloudwatch Events?"}],"answers":[{"id":"afe6e803ff73335b743f02267c6a3f17","text":"EC2 instances","correct":true},{"id":"e5c6ffd5e16261a07c150339d8a42610","text":"Amazon SQS queues","correct":true},{"id":"f4fb4c65fcc06f70081c87f3a00cb3a3","text":"Redshift clusters","correct":false},{"id":"4fc99f94726d4b95eaa8250076dc8f6f","text":"AWS Lambda functions","correct":true}]},{"id":"5d3e351c-1f62-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following constitute Multi-Factor Authentication for signing into the AWS Management Console?","explanation":"Multi-factor authentication, or MFA, adds an extra layer of protection to your user name and password when logging in to the AWS Management Console. To sign in, you would need two factors, which are 1.) the user name and password; and 2.) an authentication code from an AWS-supported MFA software app.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/features/mfa/","title":"IAM - Multi-factor Authentication"}],"answers":[{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false},{"id":"36562a3012cb05bd90eed776b4760dc7","text":"User name and authentication code","correct":false},{"id":"4cf20b6f419df88d662bb7d18bd7c7e1","text":"Password and authentication code","correct":false},{"id":"59f2c8e6be7c2804d73e2f0bad9b26e8","text":"User name, password, and authentication code","correct":true}]},{"id":"ej2zjxm0-a6xk-q2af-mol8-3c9zwje8qxyh","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans features a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system?","explanation":"Both the Business and Enterprise support levels offer a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system. Developer is < 12-hour response time in case of any system impairment. Basic does not offer any support for system impairment. Individual is not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]}]}}}}
